A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Secretary's Office, Biographical Files, RG 15 FA1280
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Field Staff and Former Staff, Transferred to RAC 1982; 6; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
  - Germino, Dante Lee (Box 58)
  - Goldschmidt, Maure L. (Box 58)
  - Helleiner, Robert H. (Box 58)
  - Jackson, Robert H. (Box 58)
  - Jensen, Bartell C. (Box 58)
  - Leonard, David K. (Box 58)
  - Leys, Colin T. (Box 58)
  - Maxwell, W. David (Box 58)
  - McIntosh, William A. (Box 58)
  - Miller, Robert W. (Box 58)
  - Okun, Bernard (Box 58)
  - Payne, George C. (Box 58)
  - Posin, Daniel Q., Jr. (Box 58)
  - Roseberg, Carl G., Jr. (Box 59)
  - Rupert, Joseph A. (Box 59)
  - Russell, Thomas G. (Box 59)
  - Trant, Gerald I. (Box 59)
  - Yerkes, William D., Jr. (Box 59)
  - Aannestad, Elling (Box 59)
  - Allbaugh, L. G. (Box 59)
  - Askey, Arthur G. (Box 59)
  - Bates, Marston (Box 59)
  - Bauer, J. M. (Box 59)
  - Beal, George J. (Box 59)
  - Bevier, George (Box 59)
  - Bohstedt, G. (Box 59)
  - Boush, G. Mallory (Box 59)
  - Brackett, Elizabeth W. (Box 59)
  - Carr, H. (Box 59)
  - Carter, Joseph C. (Box 59)
  - Day, Edmund Ezra (Box 59)
  - Deane, Herbert A. (Box 59)
  - Doyle, William J. (Box 59)
  - Dyer, Brian R. (Box 59)
  - Elderton, Marion (Box 59)
  - Eller, E. (Box 59)
  - Elmendorf, John E., Jr. (Box 59)
  - Emerson, Edward (Box 59)
  - Eversole, Henry Owen (Box 59)
  - Hackett, L. W. (Box 59)
  - Hahn, R. G. (Box 59)
  - Hooland, Carl I. (Box 59)
  - Hydrick, John L. (Box 59)
  - Johnston, M. (Box 59)
  - Kendrick, J. F. (Box 59)
  - Kitchen, Stuart (Box 59)
  - Lane, F. C. (Box 59)
  - Leach, Charles N. (Box 59)
  - Loomis, W. (Box 59)
  - Lyle, Floyd (Box 59)
  - Mahaffy, Alexander (Box 59)
  - McIntosh, W. (Box 59)
  - Milam, D. F. (Box 59)
  - Mosely, P. E. (Box 59)
  - Moss, L. (Box 59)
  - Muench, Hugo (Box 59)
  - Noll, A. M. (Box 59)
  - Payne, George (Box 59)
  - Pitner, J. (Box 59)
  - Proctor, G. W. (Box 59)
  - Rickard, E. R. (Box 59)
  - Sasse, B. (Box 59)
  - Sawyer, W. (Box 59)
  - Smillie, Wilson G. (Box 59)
  - Smith, H. (Box 59)
  - Soules, J. I. (Box 59)
  - Stephan, Frederick F. (Box 59)
  - Stevens, D. (Box 59)
  - Strode, George (Box 59)
  - Struthers, R. (Box 59)
  - Taylor, Richard M. (Box 59)
  - Tennant, M. Elizabeth (Box 59)
  - Washburn, Benjamin E. (Box 59)
  - Willits, Joseph (Box 59)
  - Wilson, D. (Box 59)
  - Wood, Bryce (Box 59)
  - Miscellaneous - A-Z (Box 59)